Speaker 1 (higher-pitched voice): He's gotta be strong and he's gotta be fast and he's gotta be fresh from the fight I need a hero I'm holding up for a hero till the morning and night He's gotta be sure and he's gotta be smooth and he's gotta be love till the night I need
Speaker 2: a hero I'm holding up for a hero till the end
of the night - Man!
Speaker 3 (higher-pitched voice): Jan, I love you guys.
Do we
Speaker 3 (higher-pitched voice): need some
Speaker 4: heroes? Do we need some heroes or
what? Actually, I
Speaker 5 (higher-pitched voice): see a lot of heroes in this room. I see a few of my personal heroes. Floyd, I see you
over
Woman 6: there. I see so many members of my team who have worked so hard.
Woman 6: Over the last 10, 11
Speaker 7 (higher-pitched voice): months to make sure that we are running a great campaign for the people of this great state. Thank you for being heroes. How many of you are door
Speaker 8 (higher-pitched voice): knockers the last couple of months through 115 degree heat? Wait, raise your hand if you've been a door knocker.
Okay, those are
Speaker 8 (higher-pitched voice): the, honestly?
Speaker 8 (higher-pitched voice): Those are the real
Woman 9: heroes, because it's about 115 degrees, and
Speaker 10 (higher-pitched voice): they've been knocking on 900 doors every single day. I love you guys. Thank you
so much.
Woman 6: I see our donors, people who reached deep into their pockets, some pulled $20 out,
Speaker 11 (higher-pitched voice): and that was difficult, because let's face it, we're living in Bidenomics, and it's not working out very
well. And
Speaker 11 (higher-pitched voice): then there's people who pulled a lot more than that out, and I appreciate every one of you. You truly are American heroes,
and...
Speaker 12: I'm going to go real personal here with my favorite heroes, which is my husband, Jeff. I just saw him disappear somewhere.
Speaker 13: He's my--there he is, right here. Say
hi to
Speaker 11 (higher-pitched voice): Jeff. He's awesome.
I've
Speaker 11 (higher-pitched voice): met him in Arizona. I married him in Arizona and little did he know that we would be on this wild ride And he's been not only he gets me around. He drives me. He protects me This guy will protect me. This guy will protect me if anybody wants to hurt me.
He will protect me
Speaker 11 (higher-pitched voice): and He's my confidant. He's happy to sit in silence with me We've all had
Speaker 12: those long days where we just want to sit silently with someone and I love you so much Jeff
Speaker 12: Thank you.
And then my
Speaker 10 (higher-pitched voice): kids, you just saw my firstborn, Ruby. How awesome is Ruby?
And you're going to meet my son,
Speaker 14 (higher-pitched voice): Leo, in a little bit. He's
Speaker 11 (higher-pitched voice): incredible as well. Just so blessed. There's so many heroes. But I think we all share one common hero.
And I
Speaker 11 (higher-pitched voice): think I'm safe to say that we think of our favorite president, Donald
Speaker 15: J. Trump, as a hero, right?
Speaker 14 (higher-pitched voice): His support, his advice, his friendship, and his strength. That guy is bulletproof. He's literally bulletproof,
guys.
Speaker 17 (higher-pitched voice): Trump is bulletproof. He's got God. Who said that? He's got God. We've got God. We've got God. Somebody said
Woman 9: to me the other day, "God saved President Trump."
And I
Speaker 14 (higher-pitched voice): said, you know what? I think God saved us when
you
Speaker 18: saved President Trump. I really do believe that. So
we
Speaker 14 (higher-pitched voice): all love you,
Speaker 19 (higher-pitched voice): President Trump, and I want to thank him. But you know what? He can't do it alone. It's not about one man. It really isn't. He can't do this alone. He needs backup in Washington, D.C.
He needs Barry Lee! Barry Lee! Barry Lee! Barry Lee! Barry Lee! Barry Lee!
Kerry, Kerry, Kerry, Kerry,
Woman 20: Kerry. He needs backup in Washington, D.C., and I'm going to be his backup.
That's right.
Woman 9: If you're awake, and I know President Trump, he's probably awake, and he's probably watching, hopefully not the fake news. President Trump, I've got your six. I've
got it.
Arizona, I
Speaker 11 (higher-pitched voice): stand before you today to officially accept your nomination as the Republican candidate for the United States Senate from the great
state of
Speaker 22: Arizona! Now,
I want to thank my
Speaker 10 (higher-pitched voice): opponent, Sheriff Mark Lamb. Actually, I hate to call him my opponent.
Speaker 5 (higher-pitched voice): He's my friend.
He's
Speaker 5 (higher-pitched voice): my friend.
Mark Lamb is my
Speaker 5 (higher-pitched voice): friend. He's great. You're
Speaker 10 (higher-pitched voice): right. Thank you. Mark Lamb is fantastic. Both Mark and Janelle are my friends. I think
Speaker 11 (higher-pitched voice): of his family as friends. And he's a member of law enforcement. Every day he goes out there and puts it all on the line. Amen. We appreciate you, Mark. He
ran a
Speaker 11 (higher-pitched voice): great
Woman 6: campaign based on, we never hit below the belt.
Speaker 23: which is so rare in politics. I'll never forget when we did our debate on May 23rd. Yes, we
Speaker 11 (higher-pitched voice): did, by the way, the media lies. We did a debate on May 23rd. Yeah, you're all going, wait a minute, yeah, the media lies.
Speaker 24 (higher-pitched voice): And when we were doing this debate,
I
Speaker 23: thought, wow, he had an opportunity to really hit below the bell, to really go dark and deep. And he didn't do it. And I thought, that is a great man. That is a man of great character.
We
Speaker 23: stuck to the issues. We talked about
Speaker 15: the issues, what was important. And I really want to thank Mark. Mark, I know that we're going to be working
Speaker 10 (higher-pitched voice): together in the future. I know we both want to save America, and I look forward to working with you. Thank you, Mark. I
also want to
Speaker 25: thank the people who voted for me. I'm pretty sure everybody in this room did.
Thank
Speaker 26: you very much.
Speaker 11 (higher-pitched voice): you I actually had a friend who I thought was liberal who texted me this morning and
Speaker 23: said I voted for you and I want to be there tonight but I don't like crowds so good
Speaker 27: luck and it tells you that the tide is changing right now so excited
so excited
so thank
Woman 28: you everyone who voted for me
Speaker 14 (higher-pitched voice): thank you for my friend who said all 16 members of my family voted
Speaker 11 (higher-pitched voice): for you today I thank you for that I thank you if I'm the first Republican you voted for I thank you if I'm the 50th Republican you voted for and I also want to talk
Speaker 15: to the people who didn't vote for me and invite you to join in this amazing America first movement we
Speaker 29: invite everybody
in right
because
Speaker 11 (higher-pitched voice): it's gonna take each and every one of us at this moment we got to come together people you know that I don't need to tell you okay don't start singing someone's about ready to start doing a music video over here
we got
Speaker 11 (higher-pitched voice): to come together as Americans we have watched what has happened over the last three and a half years and frankly we only have three and a half months to save this country who
Speaker 30: is ready
to save this country
This is an
Speaker 31: all-hands-on-deck moment, okay? All hands on deck.
Speaker 14 (higher-pitched voice): It's going to take people from all walks of life. It's going to take Trump Republicans. I think we've got
a room full of them here.
Woman 28: It's going to take traditional Republicans. I think we've got a few. How many traditional Republicans? Great.
Speaker 14 (higher-pitched voice): We love you.
It's
Speaker 14 (higher-pitched voice): going to take conservatives, independents, libertarians, even some disaffected Democrats. How many
Woman 9: former Democrats, how many people in here have voted Democrat at least once in their life? There we go.
Woman 28: We got a few of them in here. Honestly, I don't care if you're 18. Wait a minute. That started the conversation, by
the way.
somebody said
Woman 9: I didn't know you voted Democrat before that's okay it was ten and a half million Obama voters who
Woman 32: gave us President Donald J Trump and I don't hear if you're 18 years old
Speaker 33 (higher-pitched voice): and you are just graduated from high school or if you're 81 and you're trying to enjoy your golden years if you're married if you're single if you're gay if you're straight if you're proud if you're white If you
Woman 32: love this country,
welcome.
Woman 32: Welcome to the America First movement, we love
you! I'm going to be
Speaker 10 (higher-pitched voice): really
Speaker 11 (higher-pitched voice): honest because as Reverend Maupin talked about, I've been covering this state for a long time. I know you think I'm 29, I've been around a lot longer than that.
Speaker 11 (higher-pitched voice): I covered this state for 27 years,
Speaker 15: and I feel like I know the people so well. I always joked I had an intimate relationship with the people. And I say that because I did the evening news, and I would be stopped when I was at the grocery store on the street, and people would say, "My husband
Speaker 34: and I were in bed last night watching the news, watching you." And I said,
"I
Speaker 35: feel like I have an intimate relationship with you."
So I
Speaker 35: have an intimate relationship with the
Speaker 11 (higher-pitched voice): people of Arizona and I have a feeling we get we have a lot more in common than people think You know, we agree on far more
Speaker 12: than we disagree on and we've got to move past the Disagreements and focus on what unites us so we can start accomplishing something for this country. You guys okay with that?
I love
Speaker 36: you. I love you. Thank you.
I
Speaker 36: - In the Republican Party, we do have our differences because
Speaker 24 (higher-pitched voice): we like to debate, right? But I think we agree on 95% of everything. I really do, and even, I think we agree with our Democrat friends on maybe
Speaker 19 (higher-pitched voice): 80%, possibly. Let me tell you this, I know some Democrats, okay? And the Democrats I know want a
Woman 9: secure border. They really do. The Arizonans I know want a secure border.
The
Woman 9: Arizonans I know,
Speaker 37: whether they're Republican or Democrat, they want a great education for their kiddos. We pour a lot of money into our education. We want to get a
Speaker 38 (higher-pitched voice): great result. They want safe streets. They want safe neighborhoods. They want to know that if they
Speaker 15: want to go for a bike ride or have the kids play in the front yard, they're going to be safe. They want to know that they're going to be safe. The Arizonans I know don't want war and
Speaker 14 (higher-pitched voice): poverty. They want peace and prosperity. Right?
Speaker 14 (higher-pitched voice): And we got that with President Trump by the way. So if you think this is a battle between Democrats and Republicans, you're still sleeping. This is not a battle between Democrats and Republicans. That means you've been listening to the
fake news too
Speaker 14 (higher-pitched voice): long. This is not a battle between Democrats and Republicans. This is a battle between good and evil.
Speaker 14 (higher-pitched voice): This is a battle between the people who want to destroy
Speaker 25: this country and the people who want to save America.
Our country is at a crossroads. The
Speaker 15: challenges we face are not Democrat-Republican challenges. The party is...
It
Speaker 15: doesn't matter. It doesn't matter if you're at the pizza party, the pool party, the Democrat party, or the Republican party. Do you love this country and want
Speaker 14 (higher-pitched voice): to save this great nation for our future? That's where we are. Now the path that my opponent, Joe Biden and Kamala Harris' favorite congressman, Ruben
Speaker 19 (higher-pitched voice): Gallego,
is true.
It's very
Speaker 19 (higher-pitched voice): extreme. My opponent Ruben Gallego is an
Speaker 7 (higher-pitched voice): extreme liberal Democrat from Chicago who was handpicked to move to Arizona and try
Woman 9: to turn this amazing state into a socialist state. Ruben, we
Speaker 14 (higher-pitched voice): don't want
that. We don't want that.
Actually,
Speaker 14 (higher-pitched voice): I was shocked
Speaker 23: at the votes he had made and, you know, I'm going to let you in on something
Speaker 19 (higher-pitched voice): because you all know that I'm new to politics,
I'm not a
Speaker 19 (higher-pitched voice): politico. Thank you. That's why we love
Speaker 39 (higher-pitched voice): you, she said. Thank you. There's a thing called opposition research, have you heard about that? It's basically when you go all the history of
Speaker 40: somebody in politics, you look at their voting record, the things they've done, you know, most people in politics have a record
Speaker 40: this big, and that's not good. I have a one-page record. There's nothing
on it. You
Speaker 40: would not believe what Ruben Gallego,
after
Speaker 41: 10 years in the Congress, what his research folder looks like.
Do we
Speaker 41: have that somewhere?
Woman 9: Bring that
out.
Speaker 17 (higher-pitched voice): This is 10 years of being in Congress. Oh my god.
Let me
Speaker 17 (higher-pitched voice): see-- hold up. Let me see if I
can lift this. Oh my god. Let
Speaker 17 (higher-pitched voice): me just
Speaker 42: take one. Hold up. OK.
Speaker 43: This is Rubin's destructive voting record that is destroying
Speaker 44 (higher-pitched voice): Arizona.
Right
Speaker 45: here. I
was shocked when I
Speaker 44 (higher-pitched voice): saw it. The people who do this research said they have never,
Speaker 41: ever, in the whole history of doing research on some really...
Speaker 41: Seedy characters back in DC. They've never seen someone with such a disgusting
Speaker 46: record. He votes with Joe Biden and Kamala Harris 100% of the time Ruben
you're fired.
Speaker 47: That's right. I I
Speaker 48: mean retire
Let me just flip
Woman 6: through some of this, guys. First of all, he voted for legislation which brought us the highest
Speaker 39 (higher-pitched voice): inflation that we've seen in 40 years. That's why we can't afford anything. That's why my daughter said her generation is worried that they're never going to be able to have the American
Speaker 15: dream. We've priced a generation of people out of the American dream.
Speaker 15: That's why the retirees in Arizona are worried that their golden years are not going to be very golden. They're struggling to put food on the table.
Woman 9: I want to bring back the Trump economy, and we will.
Oh, this is a beauty. This is a
Woman 28: beauty. Ruben Gallego wants to defund the police.
Can
Woman 6: you...
He
Speaker 44 (higher-pitched voice): actually, it says right here, he marched and defunded the police rallies while our cities were burning back in 2020. He marched and defunded the police
Speaker 23: rallies, and he wanted to actually get rid of the filibuster to pass the George Floyd legislation, which would have defunded the police nationwide. This is crazy stuff.
I
Speaker 14 (higher-pitched voice): wanted to end the filibuster. I've got to give kudos to Senator Kirsten Sinema for saving the filibuster. That's her legacy, truly. Truly. She protected that filibuster, and I can promise you this. I will fight to protect Sinema's legacy, the filibuster. And I will always protect
Woman 28: the police, law enforcement. I want to fully fund our police and make our streets safe.
I don't
Woman 28: know, I have a feeling if a man were to show up into a locker room with any of your daughters, it's not gonna go very well
Speaker 14 (higher-pitched voice): for that guy, right? No.
- I will bury
Speaker 14 (higher-pitched voice): him! - And even after Gallego, like I said, he is the
Speaker 11 (higher-pitched voice): favorite congressman for Joe Biden and Kamala Harris. Even after they promised they wouldn't touch Medicare, the last two years, Kamala and Ruben have cut Medicare.
Speaker 11 (higher-pitched voice): last two years. The media is not going to report that.
Speaker 5 (higher-pitched voice): Let me tell you that if they're going to cut Medicare they're going to cut Social Security and we're not going to let them do that. I will tell you
take a
Speaker 5 (higher-pitched voice): look at that. Take a look I gotta move this thing. It's too heavy. It's too heavy. Take it. It's too depressing. Ruben is depressing. Thank you so much.
Speaker 5 (higher-pitched voice): I've got to tell you, there are literally a
Speaker 19 (higher-pitched voice): million other wasteful spending items that we can cut. President Trump and I will not lay a finger on your
Speaker 11 (higher-pitched voice): social security. You have my word.
And when you look at the
Speaker 50: character of Ruben Gallego, he's not a good guy. He's not a good guy. I'm a pretty strong woman. My daughter kind of laid
it out.
I
Speaker 51: have a soft side, and I, you know, I think a lot of moms, and how many of you are moms out there?
Okay,
Speaker 38 (higher-pitched voice): we're strong. We protect our babies, right? We're the mama bears.
But we have
Speaker 38 (higher-pitched voice): had that vulnerable moment in those final weeks of pregnancy, right? We're a couple weeks away from delivering
Speaker 50: our baby, and we're a little bit vulnerable. Ruben Gallego walked out on his wife days before she gave birth to the first poor
baby.
He
Speaker 11 (higher-pitched voice): walked out on her, served her divorce papers, and ran off with a D.C. lobbyist. This guy is not a good guy. If he's willing to walk out on his family, he will walk out on the voters of this great state. We cannot let that man in the U.S. Senate. I
know, it's
Speaker 11 (higher-pitched voice): shocking.
Speaker 11 (higher-pitched voice): He's an open border zealot against the border wall. He voted to give illegals
Speaker 19 (higher-pitched voice): that poured into this country during the Biden invasion. Not only asylum, but he wants them to be able to vote in this next election. No, Ruben.
Thank
Speaker 5 (higher-pitched voice): you. Latinos for Kerry, thank you. Not only.
Love
Speaker 52: you.
Speaker 5 (higher-pitched voice): 25% of our state, 25% of this great state are Hispanics. They are Latinos.
Speaker 44 (higher-pitched voice): They work hard. They care about their family. They care about their faith. They want
Speaker 14 (higher-pitched voice): their children to get a proper education. I always
Speaker 11 (higher-pitched voice): joke, 25% of Arizona is Latino. 75% of my family is Latino. My husband and children are Latino.
That's
Speaker 14 (higher-pitched voice): right.
Speaker 14 (higher-pitched voice): Latinos want safe streets, Latinos want a secure border, Latinos want their kids to get a proper
Speaker 11 (higher-pitched voice): education. They want to know that if they work hard, they will have access to the American Dream. And they will under President Trump, I can assure you of that.
So with President Trump
Speaker 53: in the White House,
Speaker 14 (higher-pitched voice): we will finish the
wall.
I
Speaker 14 (higher-pitched voice): think we're ready for that. We will secure the border. We will take down the cartels and we will end the scourge of fentanyl that's
Speaker 54: killing an entire generation.
I see a mama bear over
Speaker 15: there holding her little guy. He's falling asleep and she's just rocking him in her arms. This is why we're in it.
This is why
Speaker 23: she's standing there, guys.
We're
Speaker 23: about to lose this country.
We have
Speaker 55: three and a half months to save this
Woman 9: country. And dammit, I'm willing to do everything in my power to save it. Are you? I know she is.
I'm just like
Speaker 35: you. I love this country. I love America.
Speaker 14 (higher-pitched voice): Ruben voted to send 260 billion over to
Ukraine.
I'm
Speaker 14 (higher-pitched voice): never gonna do
Speaker 11 (higher-pitched voice): that. I will never ever sell out this country like some of these politicians have done. We're not sending our money over there. Guys, I know I mean we could sit here all day and talk about the problems. We could talk about how big these problems are. How many of you wake up at 3:00 or 4:00 in the morning and you just go, oh geez, what's coming at us tomorrow? I'm not the only one. I
Speaker 19 (higher-pitched voice): know
that.
These
Speaker 19 (higher-pitched voice): problems are massive. But the
Speaker 7 (higher-pitched voice): solutions are actually really simple, believe it or not. It's called common sense, right? It's common sense. So we can solve these problems with America First policies. That's the
Speaker 44 (higher-pitched voice): way we do it. President Trump showed us how to do it in that first term. He solved those problems. He had one head tied behind his back. He had the swamp coming after him. And in that first term, he solved so many problems. Imagine what he can do if he has backup in the second term in DC.
Speaker 44 (higher-pitched voice): We're going to solve it all. We're
going to
Woman 56: stop the Biden invasion. We're going to bring back the Trump economy. How
about we
Woman 56: replace indoctrination with a real education?
Speaker 10 (higher-pitched voice): Is that OK, mama? It's all common sense. We can solve these problems. And frankly, we must solve these problems for our children.
Speaker 44 (higher-pitched voice): That's what the--
Speaker 44 (higher-pitched voice): That is what the future is about. Even if you don't have kids, it's the children that are our future. And we need
Speaker 50: you in this fight with us. We, in this room, and in this country, have the most powerful weapon out there. Do you know what that is? Our voice. Our
voice. Our
Speaker 7 (higher-pitched voice): voice.
Do
Speaker 7 (higher-pitched voice): you know how powerful our voice is? That's why they're trying to silence us. 300
Speaker 44 (higher-pitched voice): million voices is far more powerful than five corrupt corporate media giants.
And we gotta
Speaker 44 (higher-pitched voice): start speaking out. Because these people in the back of
the room
Speaker 44 (higher-pitched voice): are the biggest, biggest problem. The people who they work
for
Speaker 41: are the biggest threat to this country.
Speaker 41: We're in an information war right now and if we don't speak out against the lies
Speaker 11 (higher-pitched voice): and the false narrative that they are pushing, we will lose our country. How many of you are willing to speak out,
Woman 56: ruffle feathers
and make a difference?
Woman 56: How many of you are ready to turn
off the fake news altogether?
Woman 56: How many of you have already turned
off the fake news? I thought so.
And
Speaker 11 (higher-pitched voice): you know the reason why that we have that powerful weapon, our voice, is because of the First Amendment. Now,
I know
Speaker 38 (higher-pitched voice): it's kind of hanging by a thread. We still have the Bill of Rights. It's hanging by a thread. But
it was
Speaker 41: 250 years ago that a small group of incredibly strong men knew
Speaker 19 (higher-pitched voice): that there were inalienable rights
that were
Speaker 19 (higher-pitched voice): granted to them, not by any man, but from God above. Inalienable rights.
And
Speaker 14 (higher-pitched voice): 250 years ago, they no longer wanted to be the subjects
Speaker 19 (higher-pitched voice): of a king named King George. They wanted to be free men and women, just like
we
Speaker 41: do. And I will tell you what, for them, because of them, and for them, America was just an idea. For all of us, America has been a reality. And it is up to us to ensure that America does not become a memory. So critical,
guys.
Speaker 11 (higher-pitched voice): I don't want that sleeping boy over there to just hear stories from his mom about the good old
Speaker 41: days when America was free. I want him to enjoy the freedom of this country. And I will tell you this, God placed every single one of those men 250 years ago right where they needed to be. And he placed us here right now for the reason we're going
Speaker 30: to save this
country.
The America First
Speaker 10 (higher-pitched voice): movement is the
Speaker 19 (higher-pitched voice): movement for the forgotten men and women. The new Republican Party is the party of common sense, and we welcome anybody who wants safety, security,
Speaker 14 (higher-pitched voice): prosperity, and freedom. Welcome to the
Republican Party.
It's going to take all
Speaker 53: of us Arizonans coming together to save this great nation, from Bullhead
Speaker 5 (higher-pitched voice): City to Window Rock, Yuma to Tombstone, Paige down to Nogales, from Winslow, we got a Nogales girl over here, from Winslow to Wickenburg and Phoenix up to the cool pines of
Speaker 57: Flagstaff. We Arizonans are coming together to save this state and save America.
Speaker 57: right
I feel like
Speaker 41: there's something happening here have you guys felt it lately
there's
Speaker 19 (higher-pitched voice): definitely something happening here but there's something happening in Arizona look at these numbers tonight look who won these races tonight there's something happening here in America right
now
there's
Speaker 19 (higher-pitched voice): something happening in the world right now
look at Venezuela look
Speaker 19 (higher-pitched voice): at the people look at humanity coming together
when we win
Speaker 19 (higher-pitched voice): the U.S. Senate seat we will make America safe
again how about
Woman 56: this we will make Arizona affordable
again and guess
Woman 56: what we're gonna make Arizona grand
again
I'm ready
Woman 56: for it. God bless every single one of you who came out and voted for me. God bless Arizona.
God
Woman 32: bless the United States of America. I love you guys. Let's go on and win November 5th and save our
Speaker 58: country. I love
you.
Speaker 61: Resistence fall behind, time we stop. Hey, what's that sound? Everybody look what's going
Woman 20: on. - Team come up here. Can my team who helped us win this race tonight come up here? They're the greatest team in all of politics because guess what? They're not a bunch of Washington, D.C. politicos. They're just Arizonans who love this state. Bring up my team. I want everybody who helped us win this race. Come on up, Alicia. We got mama bears over here.
Woman 20: Nick, I love you. Lisa, my god, the first
Speaker 3 (higher-pitched voice): person I ever met coming to
Speaker 63: Arizona. Aren't you
Speaker 3 (higher-pitched voice): glad that we met? One thousand percent. We're going to save this day. You all met Alex.
Oh my god. My favorite guy in the
Woman 20: whole world, Colton. Grew up in a trailer park in West Texas, and he loves America.
Woman 20: JT our newest member oh my god the mama bear club I love you guys Mitch how are you Alicia how are you oh it's so good to see all you guys guys it's gonna take all of us we're all one big team we're all one big team but we're gonna come together let's start talking to our neighbors even if they're Democrats we want them in this fight we're gonna save America I love
Speaker 64: you guys so much thank
Speaker 65: you